♪ I walked along the avenue ♪
♪ I never thought ♪
♪ I'd meet a girl like you ♪
♪ Meet a girl like you ♪
♪ With auburn hair and tawny eyes ♪
♪ The kind of eyes ♪
♪ That hypnotize me through ♪
♪ Hypnotize me through ♪
♪ And I ran, I ran so far away ♪
♪ I just ran, I ran all night and day ♪
♪ I couldn't get away ♪
♪ A cloud appears above your head ♪
♪ A beam of light comes ♪
♪ Shining down on you ♪
♪ The cloud is moving nearer still ♪
♪ Aurora borealis comes in view ♪
♪ Aurora comes in view ♪
♪ And I ran, I ran so far away ♪
♪ I just ran, I ran all night and day ♪
♪ I couldn't get away ♪
♪ Reached out a hand to touch your face ♪
♪ You're slowly
disappearing from my view ♪
♪ 'Pearing from my view ♪
♪ Reached out a hand to try again ♪
♪ I'm floating in a beam ♪
♪ Of light with you ♪
♪ A beam of light with you ♪
♪ And I ran, I ran so far away ♪
♪ I just ran, I ran all night and day ♪
♪ I just ran, I couldn't get away ♪